Cods?
Cody?
嘿 Zach
Hey, Zach.
还好吗 Cody?
What's up, Cody?
爷爷在睡觉
Papi's sleeping.
我看得出来
I can tell.
别玩这些好么？Don't play with these, ok?
好的Ok.
这些开给爷爷吃的
These are for grandpa.
好!
Ok!
爸 醒醒
Dad, wake up.
醒醒
Wake up.
拿好啦
Take these.
你今天有去外面活动筋骨吗？
Did you do your stretches today, dad?
嘿 CodyHey, Cody.
嘿 妈妈Hey, Mom.
今天过得怎样 孩子
How you doing, kiddo?
有帮我买烟吗？
Did you get the cigarettes?
给
Yeah.
嘿  Zach
Hey, Zach.
什么 姐姐?
What's up, sis?
计划有变 你能帮我照看Cody吗？
Change of plans.Can you take Cody?
我得代班 然后还要赶在Gabe出城前去见他
I've got a shift and then I was gonna go see Gabe before he leaves town.
我得送爸爸回家 Allen打电话给我说晚点见面
But I gotta take dad home and Allen called
and I'm supposed to meet up with him later.
总不能把他留给爸爸吧…
I could leave him with dad...
Cody 我们去兜风
Cody. let's go for a ride.
谢谢
Thank you.
我能开车吗？Can I drive?
起来了 爸 我送你回家Come on dad, I'll give you a ride back to yours.
没问题 去把车发动吧
Sure, go get her started.
Cody
Cody!
5号桌的
Table 5!
我跟你讲过 我今天不能做到打烊
I told you. I can't close up today.
El还没来
Derell's not here yet.
继续干活 孩子
You're stuck, kid.
这是餐馆 毕加索 不是画室
This is a diner, Picasso.Not the Louvre.
动作快 客人都在等
Come on! People are waiting.
你总算来了 我得闪了
Finally, man!I've gotta go.
Cody 咱们走
Cody, let's jet.
Gabe
Yo, Gabe!
嘿嘿 Gabe小子
Hey hey, the Gabester!
你不会是想一路滑到海边吧
You're learning to skate I see.
Cody还在车上 咱们走
I've got Cody in the car so let's go.
小鬼当车啊
Baby on board, huh?
就这么多?I'm taking you to the lot, right?
是啊Yeah, cool.
我以前常在这条路飙车
Hey you should come up to S.B.
这样可以把到不少高中妹
Wouldn't hurt to get some pussy you didn't get in high school.
你跟Tori分手了 对吧？
You and Tori broke it off, right?
算是吧
Sorta...
什么叫"算是吧"
"Sort of"...
伙计 干嘛
Dude... he's five.
他睡着了
He's sleeping.
没 我没睡着
No I'm not!
你是个小滑头
You are a sly one.
他喜欢装睡
Yeah he likes to pretend
he's sleeping.
跟你很搭
Go figure.
那个该是Allen的烟
That smells like Allen's cigarette.
谁是Allen？
How's Allen?
Jeanne的男朋友
Jeanne's boyfriend.
这星期的
Of the week...
伙计 你干嘛不去St Babara社区大学？
Why don't you try and go to Santa Barbara Community College?
你可以把我那儿当成自己的窝
You can crash at our house until you get your own place.
不用再对着同一帮人
At least get the fuck out of San Pedro.
我不认为学生这档子事最近有可能
I don't think the whole student thing is gonna happen right now.
没错 因为你还在想着什么艺术学院？
Why? Because you didn't get into that Art Institute place?
去其他地方的艺术学院试试
Go somewhere else"Art Institute place"...
不管怎样 我试过了
Whatever, it's alright.
奖学金是我的门票
That scholarship was my ticket...
可惜他们拒掉你了
Well you are the king of scholarships.
你倒可以去昂贵的私立名校啊
Got me into your ritchie rich private school.
那儿每天都有"性爱巴士"
On the shore bus every day.
有钱混球
Rich fuck.
游手粪青
Fuck you, ghetto trash.
你选好专业了吗？
You ever declare a major?
Larry说我该去读通讯传媒
Larry said I should go for Communications.
通讯传媒 什么意思？
"Communications"What does that mean?
意思就是我被包办完了 伙计
我只需要进驻他名下的某个公司
It means I'm set, dude. Larry's gonna set me up with something at his firm.
回去充当这个什么体制下的一分子
So I can go back and get some more.partying out of my system.
头发梳亮 穿黑西服开始用现金付账
Move back here, buy a couple suits.Start making some real cash.
如果想 你也可以过这种生活
You could have the same life if you wanted.
拿着Alright man.
伙计 过几天来看我 咱们一起玩 Ok?Alright dude. Come up and hang out soon ok?
好啊
Alright.
我说真的 伙计你已经放过我一次鸽子了
No, I mean it this time.You've been up once. That shit aint right.
知道了
我帮你订里程机票 你只要开车来机场
Look, I'll get you a plane ticketOr just get in the car and drive.
说定了？ Cool?
好Ok.
够酷 伙计 说话算话 花心男
Code-man. Keep it real, play boy.
你保证?Promise?
我保证Yeah.
好了 快去吧
Ok, ok, go...
我要尿尿 要尿尿...
Gotta pee, gotta pee...
- Hey.
想出去走走吗
I'm gonna go out for a session.
不 我以为你要呆家里 我刚去买过东西
No, I thought you were staying.I went shopping.
我还邀请了Allen过来玩
And I invited Ellen over.
怎么啦
What?
你形式上还是单身汉 至少就我所知除非有什么你没跟我说的
I heard you're an eligible bachelor.Not that you would ever tell me.
知道吗 你总这么跟Tori分手 有天她可能不回到你身边了
If you keep breaking up with Tori like that one of these times she's not coming back.
Jeanne Jeanne 听到回答 Cody呼叫Jeanne
Jeanne, Jeanne, come in Jeanne. Cody to Jeanne.
Cody 我现在不想玩 你看看电视好吗?
Cody, I don't wanna play right now.Just watch the TV.
别再提好吗 这话题闹心
Listen, I'm heading out. It's breaking hard.
Zach   Zach...
呆会儿见 Later, Codes.
你什么时候画的这个？
When did you draw this one?
很久以前了
A long time ago.
我妈妈以前在这儿上班就像现在你妈妈那样
My mom used to work herejust like yours.
有时我在这儿等她
So sometimes I would just wait out here...
画画解闷
and draw.
来 我教你怎么画
Here, I'll show you how.
画个圆圈在这儿
Go around there...
好 现在你来涂满
Here, now you just fill it in.
银色吧
Want the silver?
谁和你在一起？
Who would wait with you?
什么时候？
When?
你画这些的时候
When you drew these.
没人
Nobody.
爷爷呢？
What about Papi?
他发现她得回去工作时很受伤
Well he was very hurt from when he fell and broke his back at work.
他是你爸爸
He's your daddy.
是
Yes.
你是我爸爸
And you're my daddy.
不是 Cody 我是你舅舅
No, Cody. I'm your uncle.
你妈妈是我姐姐 所以我是你舅舅
Your mommy is my sister.That makes me your uncle.
Broid才是你爸
Roy's your daddy.
不 你是我爸爸
Nope. You're my daddy.
你是我爸爸 你是我爸爸...
You're my daddy.You're my daddy...
嘿 继续涂
Hey... keep drawing.
嘿 Zach
Hey, Zach!
还好吗
What's up.
嘿 Zach 你今晚待家里对吧
- Oh hey, Zach.You're staying in tonight, right?
Allen要带我去派对看演出 不少人要去
Allen's playing at the Landmine and he put us on the guest list.
看来你今晚要看孩子了 老弟
Looks like you're the babysitter tonight little brother.
我想是的
Guess so.
喂?
Hello?
嘿 小猴子
Hey, monkey.
嘿 你在干嘛？
Hey, what are you doing?
呃 你猜
Guess...
带孩子
Babysitting?
正确
Bingo!
嘿 我等会儿打给你Hey listen, can I give you a call back?
你在哪儿？Where are you?
你还在么 Zach 我什么都听不清
Are you there? Zach?
I can't hear anything.
-我还在- Uh, yeah
-嘿 我听不见你 - Hey, I'm losing you.
-我还在 - Yeah, I'm here.
-你听的见我说话吗? - Can you hear me? Hello?
Tori 我...正想着你
Tori, I was...Just thinking about you and...
喂?
Hello?
上帝啊
Jesus Christ! You fucking idiot...
总算完了 结束了
Oh my God... get the opener.
Jeanne 你他妈搞什么！
Jeanne, what the fuck?!
见鬼 有这么糟吗?
Shit, dad's mad.
我才哄他睡着  I just put him to bed.
好啦 他不是睡着了么  Oh come on, he can sleep through anything.
小点声 知道吗?
Just keep it down, alright?
他认真的？Did you get the cigarettes?
没错 来 Yeah, come here.
看来我逮住了你最新一次的不告而入
I thought your ghetto ass would be done breaking and entering by now.
那就改密码啊 混球
Change of code, bitch!
下次该把你绑车库里吗？
What are you gonna do,attack the garage next?
可能不用
That might not go over.
你也知道 根据太平洋房主唬烂公约你可能不会想跟法庭打交道
With the Pacific Bluff homeowners agreement,
wouldn't wanna set your dad in trouble with the board.
圆得好
Step-dad.
我把长板搁这儿了
I left my longboard here.
没关系 还好么 伙计
That's cool.How you doing, man?
还不错
Good, you know.
自你毕业我就没见过你了 你干嘛去了？
So I haven't seen you since your graduation.
What have you been up to?
工作喽 你呢？
Nothing. Working, you know.How about you?
我回来玩几星期 房子正好没人
I'm in town for a few weeks.House is empty, I could enjoy it.
我可以放松 理一下头绪
Clear my head a little bit.
我以为你讨厌回来呢
I thought you hated it down here?
我想念大海
I miss the ocean.
伙计 你住洛杉矶
Dude, you live in L.A.
我在那儿不玩水
I don't paddle out there.
想去玩玩吗？
You wanna go?
冲浪？Surfing?
当然Uh... yeah.
我想我还是可以教你些什么的
I suppose there's still a few things I could teach you.
你有得学了 花小子
You will soon learn, butterfly.
吹牛大师 你低估你的学生了
Perhaps master underestimates student.
放马过来吧 都市男
Bring it on, city boy!
选了个好时间上岸Looks like we picked a good time to come out.
是啊 现在涨潮了 Yeah, the tide's coming in.
你现在住哪儿呢？
Hey, where are you living now?
和Jeanne住在San Pedro
With Jeanne in San Pedro.
目前是这样 我也想存钱找地方自己住
It's just for now.
我也想存钱找地方自己住
I'm trying to save up to get my own place.
不过得离我爸近 所以有些棘手
Well close to my dad and work and stuff.
你什么时候住我那里都可以
Well you guys are welcome to come out here anytime you want.
就象以前一样呵
Just like old times, huh?
就当是Gabe
Minus Gabe.
对噢
Right.
你常看到他吗？
Hey... you see him much?
绝对 去年他还和几个朋友来看我
A bit. He came down last year with some of his friends.
这家伙是派对动物
Those guys like to party.
没错 绝对的
You can say that again.
Jeanne过得怎样？
How is Jeanne doing?
老样子
You know, the same I guess?
我尽我所能的帮她吧
I try to help out as much as I can.
我想象不出她当了妈妈
I cannot see her as a mom.
Cody一定大了好多吧
Cody must be getting big?
是啊 他都五岁了
Yeah, he's five already.
不可思议 时间一晃就过了
It's crazy. Time just flies.
相信我 以后只会更快
Trust me, it only gets faster.
也是
Yeah, I bet.
嘿 小猴子
Hey, monkey!
怎么？ 你在这儿做什么？
What's up?What are you doing down here?
等下在海滩有个篝火派对
Some beers, the dogs,and a fire on the beach.
你也来吧 有啤酒喝
Come down, grab a beer.
好 我一会儿过去   Cool, I'll be down in a sec.
好的  Alright.
你想喝瓶酒什么的吗 还是直接闪人?
Do you wanna go grab a beer or do you wanna just take off?
好啊 我去喝几瓶   Yeah, I'll grab a beer.
听起来不错   Sounds good.
你跟谁一起来的？
So who'd you come down with?
Billy
Billy.
他是谁？
Who is that?
Sean!
Shaun!
Gabe的哥哥？Gabe's brother?
是啊 Yeah.
他不怎么回来 一直待在洛杉矶
He doesn't come back much.He's been pretty MIA.
见到你真好
Nice to see you.
我也是
It's good to see you too.Going long!
你还玩吗？你打算玩还是站这儿说我坏话？
Are you gonna play or are you just gonna talk shit about me?
扔得漂亮
Nice throw.
我是Tori
I'm Tori.
我记得你 你才13岁还箍牙套 但我记得你
I remember you. You were 13 and you had crimped hair.
你们那次洗劫了红酒柜
I bought you guys wine coolers.
你好像还吐在我家游艇甲板上了
I think you puked on my parents' deck.
- Wow.
你现在还跟这小子一起吗？  You still putting up with this guy's shit?
呃 至少目前如此  Well we're both still here.
接个正好!
Right on.
这就是我不教Uman做烧鸡的原因
That's why you never tell a woman how to cook a chicken.
你就不能闭会儿嘴吗？
I can't believe you got shot by a chick.
Sean 对吗 Gabe的哥哥？
Shaun, right? Aren't you Gabe's bro?
嗯
Yeah.
我听说你在好莱坞写剧本什么的
Heard you went all Hollywood writing movies or something.
差不多吧
Yeah, or something.
怎么个状况 你还和Tori一起吗？
What's the deal? You're still with Tori then?
你是同志还是什么 她够性感了
Are you a fag? I mean she's hot.
我追她没问题吧?
So it's cool if I move in on that then?
大概真玩完了
The swell's coming in.
看样子是
Yeah it looks that way.
-Tripps和Tori
-看来是Yeah, I bet.
你们在一起好几年了吧?
You guys have been together for years.
是啊 我们现在需要冷处理一下
Yeah we're just taking a little break right now.
她是我最好的朋友
She's my best friend.
除Gabe外
Other than Gabe.
为了她好
It's all good.
你有交往对象吗？
You dating anyone?
没有 我刚分手
No, I just broke up.
是么 所以你会回这儿...
Yeah? Is that why you're really down here?
不不
No...
呃 其实是
Yeah, actally it is.
我搬了出来 我的新租约下个月才开始
I moved out of our place and my new lease
doesn't start until the end of the month.
这样啊
That's cool.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
喂
Hello?
我以为他已经被接走了
I thought we weren't gonna leave him over there.
不 别开车 Jeanne
No, don't drive, Jeanne.
我去接他
I'll go get him.
没错
Yeah.
我得走了
I gotta go.
好的
Alright.
Tori说想搭我的车...
Tori said she needs a ride so...
哦 没问题 我等下搭谁的车就回去了
That's cool, I'll catch a ride from someone.
今天玩的很开心
Great riding today.
-再见 伙计 Alright
-很高兴看到你 It was good seeing you man.
-我也是Yeah it was fun.
-再见Ok cool.
你自己回家吧
I'm gonna leave.
嘿 过来
Wait, come here...
我累了 晚安
I'm tired.Goodnight.
这垃圾是我写的?
Did I write this shit?
我的天
Oh my God.
喂 喂 有人接听吗 有人吗?
Hello! Hello! Is anybody out there?
喂 Sean
Hello... Shaun?
这他妈是谁？Who the fuck is this?
大师听不出来自己的学生了?Master does not know his own student.
学生变强了 大师变老了
Student is ashamed. Master gets old.
你哪儿找到的这个？
Where'd you find these?
哥们 它就躺在房子的角落
Dude, they were just laying around the house.
Gabe和我以前用这个能聊上几小时
Gabe and I used to stay up for hours on these.
真不敢相信这个直接连到你家
I can't believe that these
go all the way to your house.
直达大本营
All the way to the ghetto.
在那个年代可是高科技
They were the latest technology back then.
我记得你爸爸在机场买给Gabe的
I think your dad bought them in an airport.
为他那年错过圣诞节
when he missed a Christmas one year.
是后爸
Step-dad.
我记得那年 他给我买了个说话匣子
Yeah, I remember that year. I think he got me a talking dart board.
真逊
That sucks!
嘿 我这周看到你的墙画了 画的很可爱
Oh hey, I saw some of your tags today.They're sweet.
是么 Yeah?
呃 那些井架画得很不错  You've got the crane going on, looks cool.
很高兴还有人在搞艺术
Glad to see someone's doing their artwork.
嗯 有时吧
Yeah, sometimes.
今天冲浪我很开心
It was nice riding out there today.
噢
Yeah.
呃 怎么了？
What's up?.
你的电池快不行了
Your batteries are probably gonna run out.
大概有10年都没人用了
Probably haven't been replaced in 10 years.
你在听什么？
What are you listening to?
呃 没什么
Nothing...
他是个斗士 他一开始就是斗士
He's a fighter.
他想海扁他一顿
He's gonna kick his ass.
他也想很帅
But he wants to look good...
很帅的海扁他
kicking his ass.
他可以穿着那身漂亮正装去海扁他
He's wearing a sweet suit And he's gonna kick his ass.
伙计 你要脑子没坏咱们就去海滩
Dude, it's breaking overhead Let's roll to the 'bu.
我得工作
I'm working.
真的？ 太可惜了
Really? That's too bad.
好吧 待会再见了
Alright, I'll see you later then.
好啦 等等我 我去
Alright! Hold on, I'll come.
呃 你可能需要换件衣服
You might wanna change first.
来啊 伙计 出发!
Come on dude, let's go!
那儿人多得赶上马戏团了!
Dude, it's a fucking circus out there.
我会挡在小朋友前保护你
I'll protect you from the big brewery.Pussy!
我想到个更好的地方
Go... I've got a better spot.
更好的地方 开车
Better spot...
－地方不错It's nice.
－嗯 Yeah.
-很适合玩冲浪The waves are great.
-我需要回想一下它之前的样子 Just gotta figure out where this road is.
噢 那儿 就那儿
Oh right there!
小心
Careful.
你挡住后镜了 Should've told me sooner.
抱歉 抱歉 转弯 Sorry.
这地方真酷
This is rad!
抱歉从没告诉你和Gabe这里
Sorry I never told you and Gabe about this place, man.
我只是不想这儿成为每周日早上狼藉乱搞的地方
I just didn't want it to turn into the remnants of your keggers every Sunday morning.
我以前常来这儿躲避烦恼
This is my place I used to get away to come and just think.
冲浪吗？And surf?
嗯And surf.
咱们开始吧
Let's go.
你还在考虑申请艺术学院的事吗？
So you still thinking about applying to art school?
我现在搞街头艺术
I do street art now.
一样也很酷
It's cool though, you know.
你呢？
What are you working on?
呃 写书
A book.
怎么 追着上部写续集？
It's been like 3 years since the last one, right?
会更长篇吗？ Is is really long or something?
滚蛋 Fuck off.
像上部一样励志?
You sure didn't leave much out of the last one.
你读过?
You read it?
唔 太平洋的同志大暴乱太富戏剧性
Who knew there'd be so much drama inside the gates of Pacific Bluffs.
我不太懂
I never knew.
局外人永远不会了解内情的
You never really know what's happening inside.
这正是我乐见的
That's what I liked about it.
-我确实作了些润饰 到底是本小说
-就改几个名字？
- I did embellish a little bit, it is fiction.
- You changed a couple of names?
你什么时候看的？
When did you read it?
书刚一出来
When it came out.
奇怪Gabe从没提过
Funny, Gabe never mentioned anything.
我没跟他说过
I never told him.
他干嘛要跟你提
Why would he tell you?
呃 我只是一直不知道你有留意我
I just never knew that you knew about me.
新书写什么？
What's your new one about?
呃 我还在想
Still trying to figure that out.
主题还没选定
Don't really have a subject yet.
但我会有灵感的
But, I'll get it back.
希望是
I hope so.
你有才华
You're good.
-你真喜欢那本书？You really liked it?
-是的 Yeah.
你饿了吗？
You hungry?
-是啊　想去吃点什么吗?Yeah, you wanna go to the shack or something?
-当然 Yeah, definitely.
那么 你要在这儿待多久?
So, how long you staying around?
可能还有段时间
I'm gonna be here for a while.
我打算下月去巴塞罗那看朋友的  但是我没剩多少钱
I was supposed to go to Barcelona to meet a friend next month but I'm kinda broke.
找你父母借点钱啊
You should ask your stepfather for the cash.
唔 那不是我风格
That's not my style.
你有去过欧洲吗？
Have you ever been to Europe.
我去过佛罗里达一次
I've been to Florida once.
那阵子你父母带你去墨西哥了
And that time your parents took me to Mexico.
-我记得是那样That's about it.
-对噢That's right.
-别旅游过度I don't travel much.
-你该去走走 伙计 You should go, man.
可以啊 哪天吧
I'd like to someday.
我是说 去学艺术
I mean, just for the art.
没事 接吧
Go ahead, take it.
不了 没什么要紧的
Nah, it's cool.
-怎么 你们还在玩冷处理吗?What? You guys like, in limbo or something?
-嗯Yeah...
-这个我不怎么在行I'm no good at that.
-你只要多练习Takes a little practice.
他就直接辗过停车牌...
And he drives right through the stop sign.
一头冲进地里 彻底的昏了过去
And out into some field.He totally passed out.
他绝对有烂醉
He must've been wasted, man.
谁知道 这小子就这么白痴
He was totally hammered.He's a fucking idiot.
可他是我弟弟 我爱他
But he's my brother.And I love him.
也是我最好朋友 干杯
And my best friend.
干杯
Cheers!
要帮你再拿瓶吗？
I'm gonna get another... you?
-好的Ok.
-嗯
给你的
Here you go...
谢谢 伙计
Thanks, brother.
-哇噢Wow.
-你在干什么？ Woah... what are you doing?
别紧张 老兄 没什么大不了 我想看看
Easy dude, it's ok.I wanna look at it.
我没给任何人看过
No one ever looks at that.
那是Cody吗？
Wow, is that Cody?
嗯
Yeah.
沮丧的Cody?
A sad Cody.
你看得出来?
You could tell?
是啊 透过他头发上空的黑块
Yeah. And how you darkened it around his head.
不可思议
This is incredible.
而且房里也没有玩具
And there's no toys in his room.
很了不起
That's awesome.
他刚挨过骂 我还不知道为了什么
Yeah, he'd just gotten scolded.He was trying to understand why...
他来到我房间
So he came into my room.
这是他唯一能安然入睡的地方
He hasn't left yet.It's the only place he could sleep.
好 够了
Ok, enough.
我的喉结
Adam's apple.
-什么声?I'm trashed.
-绝对有东西潜进来了The cops are definitely coming.
该死!
Shit!
哇哦 你还是赶来了
What?You can make it.
Cody 咱们走
Cody, let's go.
你去哪儿了？
Where were you?
-冲浪Surfing.
-整晚？ All night?
是啊 怎么了
Yeah, what the fuck?
我只是问一声
I'm just asking.
-还要不要我开车Want a ride or not?
-走吧 Go.
Cody 我们走
Cody, let's go!
我想重申请加州艺术学院
I think I should reapply to CalArts...
什么是"加州艺术学院"?
What's CalArts?
是一所学校 伙计
It's a school, buddy.
-我明年也可以进学校I get to go to school next year.
-没错 Yep.
他们已经拒掉你了
They already turned you down.
你怎么有这想法的？
What made you think of that?
只是个想法
It's just a thought.
别期望太高
Well don't get your hopes up.
我们现在很艰苦 Zach 我不想你又一次失望
I mean we're having a hard time, Zach. I don't need you getting all down.
是啊...
Yeah...
Allen代付了房租  我可以问看他能不能帮你找个工作
Allen paints houses. Maybe I can see if he can hook you up with a job.
唔 你变重了
You're heavy.
-我等会儿进去I'll be right in.
-好 快来Alright, hurry up.
嘿 小猴子
Hey, monkey.
嘿
Hey.
我要迟到了
I'm late.
嘿
Hey.
Oh hey.
我听说最近你和Sean一起
I hear you've been hanging out with Shaun.
只是冲浪
Surfing.
你知道他吧？
Well you know about him, right?
什么？
What about him?
他是同志
He's gay.
别胡思乱想 Jeanne我们8岁就开始一起冲浪了
He's an old friend, Jeanne.We've been surfing together since I was 8.
就这样？
Yeah, well is that all?
是啊 你觉得还有什么？
Yeah, what are you saying?
-没了Nothing.
-这不就结了 Good.
Zach 我只是不觉得他是可以跟你光着上身一起玩的合适人选
Zach, I just don't think he's the best guy to be hanging out with all day half-naked...
你懂我意思 我不想让Cody受影响
if you know what I mean. And I don't want Cody around that.
什么 为什么？
What? Why?
我要迟到了 你先出去
I'm late. Get out.
好吧
Fine.
Zach 你不是基佬对不对？
Zach, you're not a fag, right?
Jeanne
Jeanne...
怎么了 你从不跟我说 我怎么知道？
You never tell me anything. How am I supposed to know?
你自己说呢
What do you think?
我应付不来这个
I think I don't wanna deal with that.
嗨 伙计
Hi dude.
-我试过打你电话I tried calling you.
-是吗 Yeah.
-听着 我只是想...Listen, I just wanted to...
-我现在很忙 I'm really busy man.
-哦 不错Yeah, that's cool.
-是啊 我也觉得Yeah, I know.
-听着 伙计...Listen, man...
-别再说 伙计 Just drop it, dude.
好吧
Ok.
嘿 Sean
Hey, Shaun.
嘿 怎么啦
Hey. What's up?
我需要帮手
I need help!
Sean 这是Cody
Shaun, this is Cody.
Cody 你好吗 我是Sean
Hi Cody, how are you man?I'm shaun.
我需要帮手
I need help.
要帮手？
You need help?
呃 好吧
Alright...
可是伙计 你完全弄拧了
But dude you've got it all wrong.
你得首先加固转角的部分
You've gotta fortify the corners of the moat first
加...固?
Fortify?
Cody 咱们走
Codes, let's go.
我还没弄好 我还要"加固"!
I'm not done, I have to fortify!
Sean 你能帮我照看下Cody吗？
Shaun, do you mind looking after Cody for a second?
没问题
We're cool.
我们去走走
Let's go for a walk.
我不觉得可以把Cody留下
No, I don't think I should leave Cody.
没事 Sean可以代看
Come on, Shaun can watch him.
放心去吧 没问题的
You guys go, it's fine.
好吧
Alright.
我们开始
There we go.
这儿可以做个巡逻索桥 快看这个
This is gonna be a sweet walking bridge.Oh look at that.
Sean跟Cody很合的来
Shaun's great with Cody.
那天的事我很抱歉
Listen, I'm sorry about the other day.
我是傻瓜
It was stupid.
快点儿决定吧 Zach
Just make up your mind, Zach.
你要不想跟我在一起 就别再那样对我
If you don't want to be together just  don't pull that shit on me
好
Ok.
如果那是你想要的 我可以继续我的生活
If it's what you want then  I'm gonna move on.
好
Alright.
你懂我的意思对吧？
You know what that means, right?
是的 Tori 我懂你意思
Yeah, Tori. I know what that means.
该走了吧
Just go, ok?
来 Cody 该回家了
Come on, Cody. Time to go.
再给我5分钟
Five more minutes.
Sean好棒!
Shaun rocks.
不行 Cody 我们回家
No, Cody. Let's go.
Sean好棒！
Shaun rocks!
我可以玩踩沙堡吗？
Can I jump on the sand castle?
不行 我们得回家了
No, we gotta go. Come on.
反正潮水也会把它淹没  你介意我们自己动手吗？
The tide's gonna get it anyway. You might as well let him have at it.
随便吧
Go ahead.
哥们 干得好
Alright man, great job!
来 小家伙
Come on, little man.
再见
Sayonara.
嘿 我想跟你谈谈那晚的事
Hey, I just wanted to talk to you about the other night.
什么事？
What?
我觉得你很有天赋
I think you're really talented.
你不该这么放弃 你该做点什么
And I don't think you should throw it away.I think you should do something with it.
就这些？
Is that it?
是的
Yeah.
晚点见
I'm late.
Tori 等我电话
Tor, I'll call...
早上好
Good morning.
几点了？
What time is it?
怎么你要走了吗？
Why?You got somewhere to go?
嗯 我得走了
Yeah. Yeah I gotta go.
等等
Wait.
听我说 我真得走了
Listen, I gotta go.
- Hey, Jeanne.
- Hey.
Cody呢？
Where's Cody?
说得好像你关心似的
Like you care.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你昨晚去哪儿了 我拨了你三通电话
Where were you last night?I called you like 3 times.
你需要我什么吗？
Did you need something?
是的 我需要知道你是否在我们身边
Yeah. I need to know you're there.
我当然在的 只要是为Cody
I'm always there.For Cody.
昨晚你就不在
You weren't last night.
你想要什么 Jeanne?
What do you need, Jeanne?
事实上 这个周末Allen会去波特兰
Actually, Allen is going up to Portland this weekend.
他打算带我一起去那边看看
He's gonna make a bid for a job.He said he'd take me.
能离开这儿对我来讲是很大件事
It would do me so much good to get out of here.
-Allen?Allen?
-是的 Yeah.
-Allen啊?Allen?
-嗯哼 Uh huh.
你能不能周末帮我照看Cody 拜托
Can you watch Cody this weekend? Please...
这个周末我已经安排给自己了
I was hoping to have the weekend to myself.
为什么?
Why?
你在跟谁上床？
Who are you fucking?
什么 你在说什么!
What? What are you talking about?
拜托 我看见你望着窗户发呆的样子了
Come on, I saw you gazing out the window.
我知道不是Tori 是谁？
I know it's not Tori.Who is it?
没人？
Nobody?
那你就该有空了
Well I guess you're free then.
Zach 你是我唯一可指望的了
Come on, Zach. You're all I've got.
我知道
I know.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 一切好吗？
Hey. Everything cool?
是的 还好
Yeah...
那你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
我等下就去上班
Going to work.
今晚来我这儿吧 我做牛排
Come on over tonight. I'll cook steaks.
呃 不行
Uh... I can't.
来啦 我会调配龙舌酒
Come on. I'll make margaritas.
烈性的哦
Strong ones.
那是谁？
Who is that?
没谁
No one.
别挂
Hold on.
那你就是有空了对吧
So you can do it, right?
我得给Allen答复
I gotta tell Allen.
好吧
Fine.
太好了 谢谢
Cool, thanks.
Sean 我去不了
Shaun, I can't.
为什么?
Why?
Jeanne周末要出去 我得帮她照看Cody
Jeanne's leaving for the weekend and I gotta watch Cody.
带他一起啊
So bring him.
不行
No.
为什么?
Why not?
你不介意？
You don't care?
当然不 那孩子很棒
No! That kid's great.
他说话有趣极了
He says some funny shit.
约会有他会很好玩的
Look, I'm turning the grill on at 8.
好吧
Ok.
来 伙计
Come on, dude.
我要这个 我要这个
I like these!I like these!
不好 你不需要那个
Nah, you don't want those.
我觉得你该穿这个
I think you should get these.
但我喜欢刚才那个
But I want real shoes.
可这个更酷哦
But these are way cooler.
好吧
Ok.
咱们走
Alright, let's go.
嘿 舅舅家的小魔怪 你好吗?
Hey! Ankle biter! What's up man, how are ya?
你...饿了吗?
Are you hungry?
饿死啦
Starving!
饿死了啊 晚饭想吃什么?
Starving? What would you like for dinner?
嘿 随便做点什么就可以
He'll eat whatever.
我好象没问他 是不是?
I don't think I was asking him, was I?
-是 No.
-我想也是 No, I don't think so.
冰箱有冷饮 想喝什么？
Cold ones are in the fridge.
-你喝什么？What are you drinking?
-红酒 我还有六瓶在酒柜里 Red. Larry had this sick bottle in the cellar.
可以尝尝
I'll try that.
很好
Alright, cool.
好 伙计 跟我说 你想吃些什么？
Alright, buddy. Lay it on me.What you gonna have for dinner tonight?
麦肯奶酪
Mac and Cheese
好
Ok.
热狗
Hot dogs.
热狗!
Hot dogs?
还有...煎饼带...
Pancakes with...
巧克力片的
Chocolate chips.
带巧克力片的 好!
Chocolate chips? Ok!
还有不要蔬菜
and no vegetables.
不要蔬菜？ 你确定？
No vegetables?Are you sure?
确定的确定？
Sure, sure?
好吧 伙计
Ok. Alright, buddy.
帮我个忙
I want you to do me a favor...
到海边去
Go look out at the ocean.
好看的涨潮就要来了
Beautiful waves coming in right now.
我来给你做饭 怎么搞
I'm gonna make your dinner.Somehow.
-我们现在还是在加州吗?Are we still in California?
-是的 伙计Yeah, buddy.
你去哪儿？
Where are you going?
家里没他要吃的那些
I don't think we have that stuff in the house.
说真的 你不用操心
Seriously, dude. Don't worry about it.
不 我愿意
No, I want to.
小孩子就该拿来宠的
Little kids are supposed to be spoiled.
我5分钟后回来好吗 来...
Besides, I'll be back in five minutes, ok?
我...过去看着他
I'm gonna go check on him.
Jeanne说她去哪儿？
Where did Jeanne say she was going?
俄勒冈
She's going to Oregon.
她说可能有工作机会过去看看
She thinks there's some job up there worth checking out.
我很赞赏你为Cody做的
I admire what you're doing for Cody.
其实你完全没必要
You don't have to.
不 有必要
Yeah. I do.
你可以选择 Zach
It's a choice, Zach.
我们是一家
It's family.
我没得挑
I'm the only one left.
这点你很像你母亲
You get that from your mom.
是 我知道 笑我吧
Yeah, I know.Lucky me.
过来
Come here.
怎么?
What?
过来
Come here.
我得去看看...
I need to go check...
不要紧 他睡着了 没事的
He's fine. He's asleep.
你们真的不留下过夜?
He's ok. Just come here.
我不想他醒来发现自己在陌生地方
You sure you guys don't wanna stay?
我不在身边他会不习惯
He doesn't like waking up in strange places.
好的 拿着这个
Gets enough of that when I'm not around.
这是什么？
Take this.
加州艺术学院的申请表
What is it?
Sean 我不会再走这条路
CalArts application.
拿着
Shaun, I'm not going down this road again.
谢谢今晚的款待
Take it.
晚安
Thanks for tonight.
拜
Ok.
你马上就回洛杉矶吗？
So you gonna head back up to L.A. soon?
在这儿我很开心
I'm pretty happy here.
嘿 你干嘛不跟我一起走?
Hey... why don't you come with me?
是啊 好啊
Yeah, right.
我说真的
I'm serious.
我们一起走 我住的离加州艺术学院很近
You could come with me.I live right near CalArts.
你很美
You're so beautiful.
闭嘴
Shut up!
你需要学习接受赞美
Hey, learn to take a compliment.
谢谢
Thanks.
我很高兴你在这儿
So glad you're here.
我也是
Me too.
哟 老哥 你在哪儿?
Yo, bro. What do you know!
Gabe！
Gabe!
快 快
Come on, come on!
Seanny男孩
Shaunypoo!
Gabe回来啦
Your little brother Gabe's back!
我的娇滴老大哥在哪儿？
Where's my princess big brother?
你在留男人睡觉吗？
What? You got a guy in thereyou slut?
没
No!
噢 女人？
Ooohh, a girl?
嗯啊
Yeah, right!
你干嘛这么鬼祟?
Did I interrupt your beating off, or what?
我在睡觉!
No, I was sleeping.
睡觉? 锁着门睡？
Sleeping?With the door locked?
Ok 怪胎
Ok, weirdo...
噢嘿 过来 老弟
hey, come here dude!
-见到你真好 老哥- Good to see you too, bro.
-我也是I missed you so much.
你可回来啦
There it is, yeah.
伙计 你怎么还在这儿?
Dude, so what are you doing here man?
我以为这周你会搬去新地方
I thought you were moving into your new place this week.
没 还没
No, no.
可能我觉得...
The thought of...
搬去新地方 让人觉得沉闷
moving into an empty place is just depressing, you know?
是吗? 这儿也没什么东西啊
Yeah? Well it's pretty empty here.
你没事吧？
You doing alright?
嗯 没事
Yeah, I'm good.
-你确定?You sure?
-嗯 Yeah!
我听说那段时间你很难过
I heard it was pretty tough there for a while.
是很难过
Yeah, it was tough.
别担心 罗密欧 你会找到新男友的
Well don't worry, Romeo. You'll find a new one.
是啊 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
那你准备好换上粉红Gucci衫和几个铁哥们一起去玩了吗？
So, you ready to hang up your pink Gucci suit and come bail out with your real friends?
好啊 没问题
Yeah, ok.
我给Zach打电话
Right on, I'll call Zach.
好啊 你决定
Ok, good.
那是谁？
Who was that?
June可能今天来打扫过
June's probably cleaning today.
但是June一般周二才来
But June comes on Tuesdays.
好像是哦
Yes she does.
可怜的家伙 我不知
Pool guy? I dunno.
你还好吗?
You ok?
-嗯 Yeah.
-你看上去像吓傻了 Yeah? You look a bit freaked out.
没有 我只是累了
No, I'm just tired.
-好吧Alright.
-只是累了 Just tired.
我得去搜刮冰箱看有什么垃圾食品     我他妈饿坏了
There anything good to eat in the fridge or is it stocked
with low-carb fag food cos I'm fucking starving man.
里面一堆垃圾食品
Just a lot of fag food.
哟 汉堡男孩
Yo, burger boy.
怎么啦？
What up?
你怎么在这儿？
What are you doing down here?
呃 Sheri回来过周末  我跟她说来我那儿...
Cherie's back in town for the weekend.  Told her I'd come down.
是吗 我还以为私校里有大把的小妞
I thought there's plenty of pussy in S.B.
是 可她们太爱吊你胃口
Oh yeah. But the girls there are fucking teases man.
不扯了 派对在周五晚上
Whatever. Party's on for tonight.
一堆人要来
Everyone's coming.
我们去玩急速冲浪
We'll go grab a quick surf sesh...
现在就去?
and get started.
半小时后我才有空
I'm not off for another half hour.
很好 谁把冲浪板修好了？
No worries. I already fixed your spare board.
你留在我家那个 我回来发现已经修好了
The one you've been keeping at the house.
装了护垫 打过蜡
I saw it out back and I fixed it. Grabbed it, patched it all up...
噢 那个啊 我放那儿好久了
Oh yeah... that board. Man, I left that there a while ago.
随便啦 那5点钟见了?
Whatever.So I'll see you around five tonight?
-好的 Ok.
-很好 Alright, cool.
T恤不错
Nice shirt, by the way.
最近有什么新闻?
Dude, so what's the latest?
你和Tori真的没戏了？
Are you and Tori really over this time?
嗯
Yeah.
很高兴听到 也是时候了
Glad to hear it. It's about time.
那你最近怎么过的？开始打野战了?
So what are you doing then?Just playing the field?
这儿随手一抓就有大把小妞
I talked to a bunch of people and no one sees you anywhere.
大家都走了
Everyone's gone man.
噢 你们在这儿
Yo, there he is!
终于到户外活动了啊 老人家
You lasted pretty long out there, old man.
噢 我的老哥与长板
My big bro on a longboard.
从没想过会有这么一天
Never thought I'd see the day.
是吗 过个十年你再跟我说这句
Give me 10 years and call me back about that.
是吗 我从没滑过长板(长板一般是慢划和初学者用)
Yeah, right. I'll never be on a longboard. Ever.
我都感到难为情
Alright, I'm getting beers.
怎样 宝贝?
What's up, babe?
Sean 你!
Shaun...
Sean 收敛些
Shaun, just chill.
嘿 Cods
Hey, Codes.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
Cody 你先回房间待会儿
Cody, go to your room for a second.
告诉我你只是有些困惑
Please tell me that he's just confused.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
Zach 为什么你不跟我说？
Zach, why didn't you tell me?
说什么？
Tell you what?
Ok 你的困惑是一回事
Ok, your confusion is one thing...
但把Cody也牵扯进来就太操蛋了
But bringing Cody into this is just totally fucked.
我没把他牵扯到任何里面!
I didn't bring him to anything!
－你带他去见Sean!You brought him to Shaun!
－他喜欢Sean!He likes Shaun!
Sean好过那个...
Shaun's better than...
不说那个了 不关Sean的事这是关于我们
You know what, forget it.It's not about Shaun, it's about us.
关于我们家
It is about our family.
有什么关系?
What about it?
Cody失去了父亲 他需要你 他需要一个正面的男人做楷模
Cody lost his father. He needs you. He needs a positive man in his life.
对不起 我不是Allen
I'm sorry I'm no Allen.
你什么都不懂 他只是个孩子
You don't know shit. He's a little kid.
他不会明白你那些
He's not gonna understand this.
在经过他妈的这么几年后?
You mother of the fucking year now?
噢 去你妈的
Oh fuck you.
没有我你早成什么样了
He'd be lost without me!
去你妈的 Zach
Fuck you, Zach!
Zach 你想把这个家搞垮么？
Zach, are you trying to fuck up our family?
是啊 Jeanne 这就是我想做的
Yeah, Jeanne.That's what I'm trying to do.
要知道Cody是因为我才知道什么叫家的
You know? Cody has a sense of family because of me.
妈妈死后我遗传了那该死的基因
Mom died and I got the family fucking gene.
哦 是家里的基因让你在外面搞同志的？
Oh, I see. So it's the 'family' gene that's making
you run off and have your big gay wedding?
你让这个家感到骄傲了?
You gonna make the family proud?
你在害怕什么?
Is that what you're scared of?
这跟Sean或者我无关
This isn't about Shaun, or me.
这是关于你被抛弃
This is about you being left.
而我是唯一没扔下你不管的人
I'm the only one who hasn't run off on you.
真贴心啊
Sweet.
继续啊 继续羞辱我啊
But go ahead, judge me.
我无所谓 你说对了
I don't care. You know? You're right.
没错 男人一个个抛弃我
Yeah, guys have left me.
但是Zach 现在你完全就是个混球
But, Zach, now you are just a Summer fuck, ok?
你跑去干男人的屁眼 好棒啊
You've reduced yourself to a little piece of ass
你对自己真不错啊
so, bravo! You are doing really well for yourself.
你有想过这会给他带来什么吗?
Do you think that is a good upbringing for him?
-我有Yes.
-有吗？ Do you?
不 我不知道 不知道
No, I don't know.
如果你有想过 你觉得会需要对我对Gabe 对Tori隐瞒么？
Well... if it is do you think you'd have to hide it from me, from Gabe, from Tori?
不 不 我不知道 行了吗?
I don't know!I don't fucking know, ok?
我只想知道什么对Cody最好
I just want what's best for Cody.
我也是
Well so do I!
对不起
Sorry.
上帝
Oh God.
嘿
Hey.
我需要点时间
I need some time.
我不知道这是不是我想要的
I just don't know if this is really what I want.
看上去像是你想要的
Seems like what you want.
我不知道这个...
I just don't know if this is what I want.
可不可以持久
For good.
这是什么意思？
What's that supposed to mean?
这对我并不像你那样轻松
It's not as easy for me as it is for you.
我对这完全陌生
You know, this is all totally new to me.
我们可以搞定Gabe...
We'll get through the Gabe thing...
不 不是那个 Sean
No it's not that, Shaun.
你不明白
You just don't get it, ok?
我不能要什么就提出什么 I can't just take whatever I want.
我的生活不是那样 My life is not like that.
你永远不知道要什么 除非你提出来
You'll never get what you want unless you take it.
提出来?
Take it...
你和Gabe习惯了指着什么提要求You and Gabe have always been able to point and take.
当然没问题No questions asked.
你不懂别人的生活不是那样  这真他妈的无知
You don't realize it's not like that for other people.It's fucking ignorant.
噢 那你和Jeanne就整天埋怨别人 因为你没法替自己着想?
Oh and you and Jeanne just blame everyone elsebecause you can't do anything for yourselves?
你管这叫什么?
What do you call that?
听我说 操
Look... fuck!
你干嘛这么对自己?
Why are you doing this?
因为我是个情绪化的同志 Ok?
Don't go all emotional and faggy on me, ok?
什么?
What?
我厌恶了做你的梦中情人 Sean
I'm sick of being your childhood wet dream, Shaun.
你另外找人性幻想去
Find another fucking fantasy!
知道吗 你是他妈的懦夫
You know what? You're a fucking coward!
我说完了
I'm done.
你是懦夫
You're a fucking coward.
我说完了
I'm done.
出去!
Get out!
我们打烊了
We're closed!
怎么了 老兄
What's up, bro?
好啊 伙计
Good, brother.
妈的 我酒现在还没醒
I'm so hungover...
厨房收了 要不要来杯咖啡？
Kitchen's closed.Do you want a coffee?
好 谢谢
Yes, please.
你还好吧
So what's up?
你没说一声就走了 昨晚没见你离开
I'm taking off later today.Never saw you leave last night.
-那么...So...
-那么?So?
为什么你不告诉我?
Why didn't you tell me?
告诉你什么
Tell you what?
我不介意 一点也不
I don't care... at all.
我不懂你说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你一直...都知道吗?
Have you always known?
说真的 伙计
Seriously, dude.
Ok
Ok.
其实上是我老哥怪的离谱
The fact that it's my brother is totally weird.
我知道
I know.
不 就是…
No, like...
是很怪很怪那种
really really fucking weird.
好了 我懂了 对不起
Alright, I got it.I'm sorry.
别说对不起
Don't be sorry.
别告诉别人 好吗?
Don't tell anyone, ok?
好
Ok.
这么说你有过其他男人了?
So are you going with other guys?
不是
No!
听说他们口技更好 他们口技是不是更好?
I heard they give better head.They give better head, don't they?
伙计 别说了
Dude, stop!
-他们做深喉吗?Do they swallow?
-Gabe
门外那个性感吗？
Do you think he's hot?
给我他妈闭嘴!
Shut the fuck up, dude!
好吧
Fine.
-那么 你昨晚去哪儿了So, where'd you go last night?
-睡我车里了I slept in my car.
你为什么不来我家?
Why didn't you just crash at mine?
这不一定改变什么
This doesn't have to change things.
不会改变什么? 你说得对 Gabe
Doesn't change things?You're right, Gabe.
我是你之前倾吐的对象 记得吗?
I used to be the guy you came and talked to, remember?
在Sean之前?
Before Shaun.
这对我来讲也不轻松
This isn't exactly easy on me.
你不轻松 没错
This isn't easy on you, right?
算了 已经结束就别再提了
You know what? It's over anyway.So just leave it, dude.
我还要收拾 你得走了
I've gotta clean up and you've gotta leave.
我们还是兄弟对吗?
Hey, we're still bros, alright?
我说真的
I mean it.
过来
Come here.
我能进来蹭一晚吗?
Can I please just come in and crash?
Jeanne
Jeanne?
什么事?
What?
你看见我的材料了吗? 我到处都找不到
Have you seen my portfolio?I can't find it anywhere.
我不知道
I don't know.
我申请加州艺术学院的材料
The portfolio I was putting together for CalArts.
没 我没看见
No, I haven't seen it.
-今天几号?What's today?
-好象30号 I think the 30th.
操!
Fuck!
Zach 你干嘛 他们不是拒掉你了吗?
Zachy, what are you doing?They turned you down.
为什么还要再经历一回?
Why do you wanna put yourself through that again?
只是想再给自己一次机会 知道吗?
I just thought I'd give it another shot, you know?
别费神了 那里到处是有钱小孩画画最后通过关系摆进艺术店铺里面
Well don't bother. That place is full of rich kid painters
and they're all gonna end up working at art stores anyway.
是啊 可能吧
Yeah, maybe.
海洋馆招人 要我帮你说句好话吗?
They're hiring at the Ocenette.Do you want me to put in a good word?
这工作不错啊
It's a good job.
-有钱进账We could use the money.
-好吧
为什么我们再也没见到Sean了？
How come we never see Shaun anymore?
有时候就这样 Cody 人们离开
Sometimes that happens, Cody.People leave sometimes.
他们为什么要离开?
Why did he leave?
很复杂 大人的事
It's complicated. A grown-up thing.
就算他离开 我们还能跟他打招呼吗？Can we say hi to him even though he left?
他好酷哦He was cool.
不 有时人走了就再也不回来
No.Sometimes people leave and never come back.
像我爸爸？
Like my daddy?
是啊 Cody 就像你爸爸
Yes, Cody. Like your daddy.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 Jeanne
Hey, Jeanne.
我得去陪他 他心情不好 让你知道一下
Rick is on today and he's a nightmare.So steer clear.
知道了
Got it.
走吧 Cody
Hey, Cody. Are you ready?
把笔给我
Give me your pen.
再见 小家伙
Bye, kiddo.
"您有一通新留言"
You have 1 new message.
嘿 Zach 加州艺术学院的Cody Burke
Hey, Zach. It's Kelly Burke, from CalArts.
我收到了你的申请材料
I got your portfolio and your application.
有些惊讶看到你又申请
Kinda surprised to see that you applied again.
但很高兴你这么做了
But really happy that you did.
我按照你给的海滨地址回了信
So I returned the portfolio to the Ocean Beach address that you sent it from.
不过在继续评估前还需要你来面试一趟
There's a couple of things I need to go over with you before I can continue with it.
听到留言请回电话给我
So give me a call when you get this.
我在20号楼 期待你回音 保重身体
I'm at extension 20 and I hope to hear from you.Alright, take care.
"重播请按4 删除请按7 回电请按8 保存请按9"
To replay, press 4. To erase, press 7.To return this call, press 8. To save, press 9.
"需要其他服务请按星号键"
To hear all other options, press star.
Jeanne 起床了 起床了
Jeanne, get up!Get up!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
睡觉啊
Sleeping.
是吗 通过药物?
Yeah, with some help.
等等 Zach 等等
Wait, Zach, wait.
Allen拿到那份工作了
Allen got that job.
嗯
Yeah?
在波特兰 我得和他一起去
In Portland and I gotta go with him.
他们给的工资很高
I can make good money there.
但他们不让带小孩
But they don't take kids.
什么叫"不让带小孩"？
What do you mean they don't take kids?
我不知道 他们就是不接收小孩
I don't know. They just don't take kids.
况且Allen也不是很喜欢小孩
Allen's not really into it anyway.
Cody可能得跟你和爸爸一直待这儿...
Cody's gonna have to stay here with you and Papi...
至少等我安顿下来
At least until we get set up.
那是多久？
With me and dad for how long?
我不清楚 六个月 也许是一年
I dunno. Six months... a year maybe?
你知道我跟爸爸合不来
You know he can't stay with dad.
我知道
I know.
可他们不能跟着我
But he can't come with me.
Zach 海滨离我们那儿没多远我可以抽时间回来
Zach, the Oceanette is not cutting it.I can make three times that up there.
还有吗?
Is there any more?
我吃饱了 要我的吗？
Well I'm full, do you want mine?
可以吗?
Yeah.
我还饿呢
I do.
喜欢吃吗？
You like it?
嗯
Yeah.
- Mom?
- Yeah.
我能跟你们去俄勒冈吗？
Can I go to Oregon too?
Cody 我跟你说过你得留下
Cody, I told you.You gotta stay here
陪着Zach舅舅 这样他才不会寂寞
and keep your uncle Zach company so he doesn't get lonely.
你能为妈妈做这事吗？
Can you do that for mommy?
喂?
Hello?
不 他不在
No, he's not here.
嘿 小猴子
Hey, monkey.
嘿
Hey.
我被录取了
I got in.
什么?
What?
加州艺术学院 他们又要我了
To CalArts, they took me back.
我不知道该怎么做
I don't know how I'll do it.
你会找到办法的
You'll have to figure out a way.
你会朝前看 不再困在这儿
If you pass it up  You'll be stuck here.
我没觉得被困
I don't feel stuck here.
不 你有
Yes you do.
Jeanne要去俄勒冈
Jeanne wants to go to Oregon.
那你也不必留下
Maybe she'll have to stay.
照顾Cody是她的责任
Cody is her responsibility.
我不能留下他
I can't leave him.
会有办法的
Figure it out.
开心点
Cheer up!
我们就不能庆祝一下吗?
Can we just celebrate?
有件事我要跟你说
There's something I really need to tell you.
我早知道了
I already know.
知道有一段时间了
I've known for a while.
如果我希望自己不是 那全是因为你
You are the only reason I wish I wasn't.
知道吗 其他都不重要
None of this other shit matters.
但我们搞砸了
But what really sucks...
我一直希望成为你要的全部
Is that I've always wanted to be everything to you.
做梦都想满足你所有想要的 需要的
Always dreamed of providing you with anything you ever wanted or needed.
你爱他吗?
Do you love him?
拜托
Oh come on...
我说真的
Seriously.
他是个好男人 Zach
He's a good guy, Zach.
你不能永远都考虑别人
You don't belong to people forever.
那还问这个做什么?
Then why bother?
这样值得吗?
Isn't it worth it?
嗯
Yeah.
- Tori.
- Yeah?
我可以住你那儿吗？就今晚
Can I stay with you just for the night?
我没地方去 我没法面对Jeanne
I have nowhere else to go and I can't face Jeanne.
当然可以
Of course.
但你休想上我
But you can't fuck me.
得了
Come on...
说点什么
Say something.
你先说
You say something.
学生表现很糟 我指那晚发飙
Student was bad.Made bad judgment call.
我没能看透
Now see truth.
你在哪儿？
Where are you?
感觉热点了没?
Getting warmer...
冷了?
Colder...
转身
Turn around.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你最好是
You'd better be.
你帮我寄的申请材料？
You sent in my application?
是
Yeah.
你来这儿干嘛?
Why are you here?
什么改变了?
What changed?
我变了
I did.
你愿意帮我吗？
Will you help me?
你说真的？
You serious?
当然 任何事
Of course.Anything.
任何事？
Anything?
是的
Yes.
我被录取了
I got in.
-太好了 Full ride.
-我就知道Yes! I knew it!
你认真的吧?
Are you serious?
这次我真想去
Yeah, I really wanna go this time.
当然
Of course.
上次是我拒绝了奖学金
I turned down the scholarship before.
妈妈 Cody 一切一切 我没法兼顾到
My mom... Cody... everything. It just couldn't work out.
我没告诉过别人
I never told anyone.
这次我真的想去
I really wanna go this time.
而且 你说过住的很近
And you did say you lived close.
好吧 咱们说定了
Well then let's do it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
我为你骄傲 伙计 我为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you, man. So proud.
-Sean Shaun!
-嘿 小家伙Hey, kiddo...
Allen 把Cody带进屋好吗?
Allen, take Cody inside, ok?
Zach 你带他来做什么？
Zach, what is he doing here?
你是想背弃我吗?
What? Are you bailing on me?
背弃？
Bailing?
Jeanne 你才是离开你孩子的那个
Jeanne, you're the one leaving your son!
如果你不喜欢这个选择 你可以留下啊
If you don't like this option then just stay.
我只等5分钟
Five more minutes!
Cody 给我他妈闭嘴
Jesus, Cody. Shut the fuck up you...
你怎么敢这么跟他说话...
Dont you ever talk to him like that!
-Zach!
-Allen!
宝贝 就当是为我好吗 为我? 求求你
Take a walk baby, please? For me. Please...
好吧
Ok, ok.
别激动Easy, easy.
- Zach, what the fuck!
我的上帝
Jesus Christ.
我进去看看Allen
I'm gonna go inside and check on him.
Sean是很好的人 Jeanne
Shaun is really great, Jeanne.
他真的关心Cody和我
He really cares about Cody...
and me.
那男人要不能跟你一起 其实会是件好事
If he can't be with you,
this is the next best thing.
我们会处得很好
I'm gonna make it work.
Jeanne看看周围吧
Jeanne, take a look around.
每个小孩都该享有幸福
Every kid should be so lucky.
除了这个你还想他什么呢?
What else could you possibly want for him?
我被加州艺术学院录取了
I got into CalArts.
我知道
I know.
你知道？
You know?
你没打算跟我说？
Were you gonna tell me?
他们说上次是你拒掉他们
They told me that you turned it down last time.
这次我不会了
I'm not going to again.
是的 你不该
No, you shouldn't.
要么接受我们
He'll be fine with us...
要么留下 你自己选择
Or stay, it's your choice.
Zach 要是这次跟Allen离开不如预期
Zach, if this thing with Allen doesn't work out...
留下跟你一起才是对他最好的
It's best that he's here with you.
照顾好自己 你保证
He's in good hands I promise.
嗯
Yeah.
准备好了吗？
You ready?
=剧终 谢谢观赏=